https://www.heralopecia.com/privacy/

About
Privacy
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
HerAlopecia is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Should you choose to provide your email address or any other personal information on any of the forms found on our site, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with HerAlopecia.
First and foremost, it is important that you know that HerAlopecia has never, and will never give your email information to *any* third party whatsoever when filling out forms, joining our email notification lists, or any other similar communication. There are no exceptions to this. We are extremely adamant about this issue, and your privacy and security will always be 100% protected.
At the time of the writing of this legally binding document, HerAlopecia provides personal information only to our shippers who use it to ship products to those who order on our store. They are prohibited from redistributing that information to anyone.
This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers the six foundation principles of fair information: Awareness, Collection, Use, Sharing, Children, and Security.
Awareness
HerAlopecia provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the bottom of every page on the site, with exception of the Discussion Forums.
What we collect
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you fill out a form to request more information, register a profile in our Discussion Forums, register for one of our many Email notification lists, or establishing an account with us in our Online Product Center. Personal information collected by HerAlopecia often is limited to e-mail address, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.
How we use it
All information collected is used solely for the purpose announced on the page where the form resides, and to support your relationship with HerAlopecia.com. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
HerAlopecia.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on HerAlopecia.com web site;
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of HerAlopecia.com and its family of Web sites, and,
(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of HerAlopecia.com, its affiliate Web sites, or the public.
Who we share it with
HerAlopecia will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your knowledge. There are no exceptions to this rule. Your personal information is provided to our shipping service and product affiliates who process your orders on our Online Product Center, but this is only to ensure safe delivery and billing of your products.
These entities and/or business partners whom we work with, including those in the United States and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.
Children’s Privacy Protection
HerAlopecia takes special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourages parents to be an active participant in their child’s online activities and interests. We abide by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requirements. Our web site is not intended for children under the age of 13 typically, and we will not knowingly collect data from them.
Choice
HerAlopecia will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Local country laws and policies are applied where they differ from those in the U.S.
Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.
Accuracy & Access
Links to third party web sites on the site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the HerAlopecia site. HerAlopecia has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policies. Thus, HerAlopecia does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so at your own risk.
Security
HerAlopecia is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use strong security encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information.
HerAlopecia.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, HerAlopecia.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.
Search for:
About Us
We're Here For You
Information, Treatments, and a thriving online Community dedicated entirely to finding Solutions for your hair.
My Newsletter
Receive My News Straight Into Your Inbox!
[wysija_form id="1"]
Don't Worry, I Don't Spam.
